wanhai.com 2019-06-17

# WAN HAI LINES LTD.

## Privacy and Cookies Policy

This website is provided and operated by Wan Hai Lines Ltd. (hereinafter called "WHL" or "the Company") which is registered at10th Floor, 136, Sung Chiang Road, Taipei, Taiwan.

WHL recognizes and respect the importance of your privacy and is committed to protecting  and processing your personal data with due care at all times. When visiting our website, WHL expects you to understand your related rights so as to feel comfortable to use all related Internet services provided by WHL. In accordance with Personal Information Protection Act of Taiwan and General Data Protection Regulation of EU, WHL hereby would notify you of the following matters in expressing the Company’s commitment of privacy protection.  

By using this website, you agree on the collection, the use and the disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this policy. If you do not agree with the terms herein, please refrain from visiting this website or online systems.

1、Purpose and Categories of Personal Information Collection

(a) In order to improve service quality and enhance services, the Company will collect your personal information within the scope of the Website, APP and Service Center by including but not limited to the following:

  1. Apply for membership of the Company.
  2. The Company's customer service. To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes

(b) By providing the Service mentioned above, the Company will collect your personal Information which is including but not limited to the following:

  1. Personal identification: including but not limited to name, occupations, address, working address, previous address, phone number, mobile phone number, instant messaging account, network platform account, mailing address and resident address, photo, fingerprint, E-mail address, electronic signature, credit card number, certificate number, record for providing network identity authentication or inquiry service, internet protocol IP address, cookie and any other information that can identify the principal.
  2. Financial identification: including but not limited to, financial institution account number, financial institution account name, credit card number, debit card number, other personal number, or account.
  3. Identification of government's information : including but not limited to ID number, unified certificate number, tax registration number, license number, and passport number.
  4. Personal description: including but not limited to, age, gender, date of birth, birthplace, nationality, voice, etc..
  5. Details of other family members : including but not limited to children, dependants, other family members or relatives, parents, cohabitants, and relatives of expatriates and mainlanders.
  6. Leisure activities and interests: including, but not limited to, hobbies, sports, and other interests.
  7. vii. Unclassified information: including but not limited to letters, files, reports, recordings, or emails that cannot be classified.

(c ) If you cannot provide the personal Information required by the relevant service, you may not be able to complete some of the services and transactions you need.

2、Processing, Purposes, Period and Area of Personal Information

(a) The Company collects, processes and uses personal information you provided for the following purposes:

  1. Operate and improve the Company’s website to provide more effective services.
  2. Avoid requiring repeated input of the same information to make the website or service easier to use.
  3. Conduct customer service quality survey and analysis

(b) Without your written consent, the Company will only process and use your personal information based on the specific purpose of collection for the purpose. Except for special situation ,legal requirements, or requirements of government agencies or regulatory authorities, the Company will never disclose your information to anyone.

(c) Period: The period of using your personal information is different according to the specific purpose of the collection, the relevant laws and regulations (eg Civil Code, Personal Information Protection Act of R.O.C. etc.), the necessary retention period required for the execution of the business (longer than the period prescribed by the laws or regulations) or the retention period set by the individual contract which is appointment for years of preservation.

(d) Area: Your personal information will be used in the Company and business office around the world of WAN HAI Group.

3、Data Transfer Abroad

(a) Under the following situations, the Company may provide your personal information through computer processing and cross-border transmission to the Company's personnel, agents, the company's contractors, agents, affiliates, associates, groups, and official authorities of the country of entry, and partners, etc. to provide immediate convenience elated services：

  1.   If the services are required from the Company's personnel, agents, the Company's contractors, agents, affiliates, affiliates, corporations, official authorities of the country of entry, and partners；or
  2. If the Company's business is transferred.

(b) The Company will make effort to ensure that its personnel, agents, contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, groups and related partners, etc., observe the terms of the Privacy notice.

(c) We promise that your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties who are not related to this service or be used other than the purposes mentioned above without your consent, except, it is used for to the investigation or use purpose of assisting the judicial authorities, or relevant authorities.

4、The Rights of the Data Subject

When the Company holds your personal information, you can exercise the following rights in accordance with Personal Information Protection Act of the Republic of China and General Data Protection Regulation of EU

  * any inquiry and request for a review of your personal information;
  * any request to make duplications of your personal information;
  * any request to supplement or correct your personal information;
  * any request to discontinue collection, processing or use of your personal information,
  * any request to limit processing your personal information,
  * any request to limit automatic decision making.
  * any request to delete your personal information. However, if your personal information processing is necessary and such information could not be deleted in accordance with the laws and regulations,, the Company may not be able to perform and reply accordingly.
  * any request to bring out your personal information.

5、Cookies

Cookies are short messages that the web server writes to the user's hard disk via the browser in order to distinguish the user's preferences. To provide better service and facilitate your participation in personalized interaction. The Company's website may provide user-related functional services through cookies. If you do not agree to the access of cookies, you may remove the cookies through the browser's settings. However, if you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use our global information network or mobile website normally.

6、Security

The Company uses a variety of advanced technologies, data appropriate technical security equipment and international, organizational measures recognized network verification procedures and protective measures to strictly protect the security of websites and your personal information.

7、Changes

The Company will regularly review this Privacy and Cookies Policy and reserves the right to amend this Privacy and Cookies Policy at any time in line with business and regulatory changes. Any new revised version of this policy will be presented on this page.

8、Law and jurisdiction

Any dispute, claim, matter of construction or interpretation arising out of and from or in any way relating to the website, including these terms, shall be governed by the law of Taiwan and be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the District Court of Taipei, Taiwan.

9、Contact details

If you have any queries, comments or updates about our Privacy and Cookies Policy, please contact [Dataprotection@wanhai.com](mailto:Dataprotection@wanhai.com) or you may contact us by sending a letter to Wan Hai Lines Ltd.- 10th Floor, 136, Sung Chiang Road, Taipei, TAIWAN.
